欢迎回到格林德尔
Welcome back to Greendale,
暨现科罗拉多社区大学中
now ranking fifth on Colorado's
按字母排序第五的学院
alphabetical listing of community colleges.
安息吧  坏小子斯林穆DJ学院
Rest in peace, Bad Boy Slim's DJ School.
本校能幸存至今  要感谢以下几位英雄
This school owes its continued existence to the following heroes.
电动汽车专用停车位
杰夫·翁格
Jeff Winger,
一位积极拥护清洁能源的老师
a teacher so dedicated to clean energy,
连停车都向电动车看齐  抢占其专用车位
he's already parking like his car is electric.
如果是你会怎样?
布雷塔·派利最近提高了人们对流浪者的认识
Britta Perry, currently raising awareness of homelessness,
反正她也没得选
not that she has a choice.
阿布蒂·纳德尔  本声明的实际撰稿人
Abed Nadir, who actually wrote this announcement
用他的话说  旨在让大家跟上剧情
for the sake of, as he put it, catching everyone up.
安妮·埃迪生  曾负责为格林德尔
And Annie Edison who led the effort to save
解决了534起重大事件
Greendale from 534 critical emergencies.
534起
534?
拯救格林德尔委员会
待办    完成
屋顶飞盘
飞盘
Frisbee!
专业飞盘
伦纳德
伦纳德  你还想霸占那盘子到什么时候
Hey Leonard, what, are you gonna Bogart the disc all day?
格林德尔
通往未来之路
计算机学院
如  雨中泪
Like tears in rain.
■
本字幕首发于字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
啥
What?
翻译    笨笨Benny    白月   天青月白
翻译    别扭大菜    爵士年代蓬蓬裙
时间轴    Spohy
后期    鱼骨头
校对/总监    爆肝の王·夕橙
精校鸣谢    greydale    鬼金属
废柴联盟
第六季  第一集
简直没法相信屋顶还能塌了
I can't believe the roof collapsed.
我们差点害死胖尼尔
We almost killed Fat Neil.
人家叫加瑞特
That was Garrett.
听到没  我们就是禽兽
See, we're monsters.
好  如果要怪到我们头上  这黑锅我背了
Okay, if they blame us for this, let me take the heat.
我还没见过监狱里啥样呢
I'd never see the inside of a cell.
我一直重复过这一天  已然过了一千年
I have been reliving this day over and over for a thousand years.
同志们  这事儿不怪我们
Guys, this is not on us.
屋顶本来就要塌了  80%的瓦砾是泡沫
That roof was gonna collapse, 80% of the rubble was styrofoam.
说到有罪  雪瑞哪去了
Speaking of guilt, where's Shirley?
你没跟他说
You didn't tell him?
我在等我们聚齐了再说
I was waiting until we were all together.
阿布蒂不习惯  波一安  喝呜阿
Abed's not comfortable with C-H-A-N-G-E.
去死吧你
Hey, screw you.
我也会拼音的
I can spell.
昌以为他们在说自己
去死去死
Screw you.
雪瑞走了吗
Is Shirley gone?
她单飞拍衍生剧去啦
Did she spin off?
现实生活里没人拍衍生剧  阿布蒂
Nobody spins off in real life, Abed.
雪瑞去亚特兰大照顾她爸爸去了
Shirley went to look after her dad in Atlanta
后来去做了私人厨师  雇主是一位聪明绝顶
and ended up taking a job as a personal chef to a brilliant,
麻烦缠身的南方侦探
but troubled Southern detective.
我跟她说好在此期间我会帮她看好三明治店
I told her I'd manage her sandwich shop while she's gone.
你真大方
Oh, that's very generous of you.
我城里有人
I have a friend in town,
需要帮忙尽管说话
every time you're gonna need help with that.
她会回来的
She'll be back.
像特洛伊一样
Like Troy?
你们这些白人
Are any of you white people
没注意到组里变成什么样了吗
noticing what's happening to this group?
我和阿布蒂需要担心吗
Do Abed and I need to be concerned?
我跟你保证  只要我还是白人领导
You have my word, as leader of the white people
就没有担心的必要
there's no cause for alarm.
跟新雪瑞打个招呼吧
Say hello to new Shirley.
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
这位是弗兰西丝卡·达特
This is Francesca Dart.
我带她来是当行政顾问的
I have brought her on as an administrative consultant.
旨在增加趣味  也是强制性地
I thought it would be fun, and mandatory for
必须加入你们这个小委员会
you to add her to your little committee.
为什么  就因为塌了个屋顶
Why, because one roof collapsed?
不  当然不是啦
No, God, God no.
我是作为朋友  给你们带新朋友来的
I'm your friend bringing you a new friend,
这新朋友接受过「不塌屋顶培训」
one with training in not collapsing roofs.
那她...别介意女士
Is she, excuse me, ma'am.
那她...是在我们之上  还是之下
Is she above us or below us?
她...
She is, woop!
有电话来了  我必须得接
I'm getting a call, here, and I'll have to take it.
弗兰  你来说明一下你的任务
Frankie, why don't you explain what your role will be,
我出去接个电话
while I leave to take this call.
我手机正在震动
My phone is vibrating,
-但...它...  -在你办公室里
- but it is - In your office, which you didn't realize,
你开始假装要接电话的时候  才想起来
when you started the fake phone call move.
手机就在人家口袋里  杰夫瑞
My phone is in my pocket, Jeffrey.
我渐渐离开  是为了出去接电话
I'm walking away, so I can get it out and answer it.
一会告诉我进展如何
Let me know how it goes.
好吧  我坐下说...
Okay, I'll just have a seat and-.
-不行...-不要
- No! - No!
-不行不行  -喂
- No, no, no! - Hey!
那是我们朋友的老座位
Our friend use to sit there.
她拍衍生剧去了
She spun off.
抱歉  那这儿呢
I'm sorry, what about here?
坐吧  那没事
Yeah, ,I guess that's okay.
行
Okay, so,
我对格林德尔在人们心中
I took an informal survey
是怎样一个存在  做了个非正式调查
to get a sense of how Greendale is perceived.
三个主题浮现出来  诡异
And three themes emerged, weird.
激昂和恶心
Passionate and gross.
现在你们还坚持抱团
Now you want to hang onto that grouping.
在市场上  我们称这个为好布鲁什
In marketing, it's what we call the Good Belushi.
我要是有根魔杖
If I had a magic wand,
我会用它来确保格林德尔不会发展扩张
I would use it to make sure Greendale never had to grow up.
或者用来砍掉「魔杖课」
I would also probably use it to cut the Magic Wand class
我没想到你们居然还真这门课
that I noticed is actually offered here,
还有「录像机修理课」  「梯子课」
as well as VCR Repair, a class called Ladders,
还有「最佳时机晃孩子课」
and when is it Okay to Shake a Baby?
至于等级制度  我是十分推崇的
In terms of hierarchy, I'm a big believer in it.
如果要有人领头  那个人必须是我
Someone needs to say, I'm in charge, and that person is me.
得由我说了算
That's my decision.
不代表我们不能合作
That doesn't mean that we don't work together,
但所有沟通交流以及决定都得经过我
but all communication and decisions will go through me.
过会我会给大家发邮件  确定下次开会时间
I'll send out an email later to set up our next meeting.
-太好了  -很荣幸见到您  教授
- Awesome. - Okay. Great seeing you, Professor.
好酷哦
Yeah. Coolios.
这疯婊子是干嘛来的
Who in the crazy bitch?
刚刚那是真的吗
Did that just happen?
你们看到她的活页夹了吗
Did you see her binder?
真是没特色
Pretty nondescript.
看起来她是个麻烦啊
Seems like she may be trouble.
老实说  算上她又多了个白人
To be fair, she's an additional white person,
显然已经成为这里的重要问题了
which has clearly become important here.
没  谢谢你
No, thank you.
能接到电话就万幸了
I, I'm just glad I was able to answer.
手机刚刚卡我口袋里拿不出来了
My, my phone got lodged in my pocket.
我知道
I know!
我猜这种事也免不了啦
I guess that is a thing.
话说  刚才说到那件事
So, you were saying about the thing,
你打电话给我的理由
the reason you were calling was,
到底是为什么来着
what were you talking to me about?
看上去不错  托尼
Looks good, Tony.
不好意思  我就直接猜你叫托尼了
I'm sorry, I just assume your name is Tony.
你的菜齐了
Here you go.
我给你的菜多加热了一会儿
I gave you some extra heat.
布雷塔  这个餐厅每周的成本花费多少
Britta, what is the weekly cost of this restaurant?
太简单了
Oh, that's easy.
我的尊严
My dignity.
看上去这个三明治摊正消耗着你的快乐
Seems like this sandwich counter is consuming your happiness and
取而代之的是烤焦的面包和累累欠债
converting it into burnt bread and debt.
所以嘞
So?
弗兰  你好
Frankie, hi.
有人搬空了员工休息室里所有的酒
Someone removed all the liquor from the faculty lounge.
很抱歉  我无法在法律上保护
I'm sorry, I cannot legally protect or insure
一所酒水泛滥的学校
a campus with free flowing booze.
可如果时刻保持清醒我就没法教书了
Well, I can't teach with free flowing sobriety.
是这样吗
Is that true?
你真的认为你是个酒鬼吗
Do you really think you're an addict?
没啊
No.
院长
Dean!
是的  我有空
Yes, I can talk.
可恶
Damn it.
你若需要帮助我一定随叫随到
I am available anytime for you.
弗兰  弗兰
Frankie, Frankie.
我有个想法能让泳池不易导电
Hi. I had an idea about how to deelectrify the pool.
这件事我已经处理好了
Oh, that's already been dealt with.
好吧  接下去  还有...
Okay, well, then, there's-.
让我看看
Oh, let's see.
完成  完成  虱子已清
Done, done, deloused.
已评估  已拆除  重建完成
Appraised, defused, rebuilt.
花生酱清完了  赶跑了  都阉了
De-peanut buttered, debunked, spayed, neutered.
进行中  重批  暴跌
Underway, resanctified, plunged,
驱逐出境  已掘出
deported and exhumed.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这个挺漂亮的
Oh, this is pretty.
我要用她来命名我做的三明治
I'm gonna name one of my sandwiches after her.
我的三明治可难吃了
My sandwiches suck.
她确实在改善格林德尔
She is improving Greendale.
可格林德尔能有什么可改善的呢
Yeah, but how much can you improve Greendale
除非完全改头换面不做格林德尔
before it stops being Greendale?
她没在这里遭过罪
She didn't suffer for this place.
她不理解这里的精髓
She doesn't understand it.
她最后肯定会伤害到一些...
She's gonna end up messing with something that-.
阿布蒂
Abed.
请解释一下时空变异  博士  说人话
Temporal mutation in English, Doc.
简单来说  总统先生
Simply put, Mr. President,
这些恐龙在十二小时内会变成
in 12 hours these dinosaurs will become-.
介意我坐这儿吗
Mind if I sit here?
时空龙
Time-asaurs.
坐吧  我重录
Go ahead, I can reshoot.
最近怎么样
How's everything going?
我有一些顾虑
I have concerns.
说来听听
I'd like to hear them.
我很担心无论从体型上还是意志方面
I'm worried you're not distinct enough for Manny
你都难以达到男保姆的要求
both in terms of physicality and purpose.
好吧
Okay.
我判断不出你是否有任何特别的缺点
I can't determine if you have any specific flaw,
怪癖  或是观点
quirk, or point of view that
能让你的加入为我们小组锦上添花
makes you a creative addition to the group.
我不知道你在说什么  但我会记下来
I don't know what that means, but I'm writing it down.
简而言之  我担心的是你作为一个新角色
My umbrella concern is that you, as a character,
预示了我所说的我们剧集的完结
represent the end of what I used to call our show,
以前我们是不合群学生组成的不可能家族
which was once an unlikely family of misfit students,
而现在是由老师和学生组成的松散团体
and is now a pretty loose knit group of students and teachers,
甚至大家彼此之间都没人同修一门课
none of whom are taking a class together in a school which,
而你的到来  让整个学院变得无比现实
as of your arrival, is becoming increasingly grounded,
我们开始思索  比如「我们的钱从哪儿来」
asking questions like, how do any of us get our money?
「我们什么时候才能毕业」
When will we get our degrees?
还有「我以前约会的那个姑娘去哪儿了」
And what happened to that girl I was dating?
而事实上我却认为这些问题更重要
As opposed to questions I consider more important like,
比如「什么是真实」 「什么是清醒」
what is real? What is sanity?
「有没有上帝」
Is there a God?
「皮尔斯的全息影像去哪儿了」
Where's that Pierce hologram?
杰夫说去年他看到过皮尔斯的全息影像
Jeff said last year he saw a Pierce hologram.
我们其他人都没看到过
None of the rest of us have ever seen it.
所以  如果皮尔斯的鬼魂在校园游荡
So, if there's a Pierce ghost on campus,
我很乐意成为头一个去抓它的人
I'd like to get a head start on busting it.
好吧  这还是我第一次
All right. This is the first
听到我是一个剧里的角色这种说法
I've heard that I'm a character on a show.
我很荣幸  我也同意我的角色会很无趣
I'm excited to be one, but I agree, I'll be a boring one.
举止怪异不是我的特长  做出成果才是
Quirks are not my strong suit, results are.
我喜欢怪胎
I love quirky people.
我来自一个几乎全是疯子的大家庭
I come from a big family of people who are literally insane.
我搬来这里就是为了照顾其中一位家人
I moved down here to take care of one of them.
但我是个特例  我很无趣
But I myself am exceptionally boring,
我对此感到很骄傲
and I am quite proud to be that way,
因为这样我就能帮助
because it allows me to help
那些不那么无趣的人  化怪异为成就
the ess boring people turn quirks into results.
这番甘于无趣的言论
That's the most interesting take on
是我听到过的最有趣的了
not being interesting  that I've ever heard.
至于我给你的剧带来的征兆
As far as what I represent about your show,
我不会给我自己或其他任何人这种力量
I wouldn't give me or anyone else that kind of power.
好剧不会一成不变  我猜
Good shows change, I assume.
我自己是没电视的
Personally, I don't own a TV.
你是第一个说这种话而我却没有
You're the first person to say that
第一时间把它们从脑海里删除的人了
that I didn't immediately delete from my brain.
谢谢
Thank you.
立刻在雪瑞三明治店召开紧急会议
Emergency meeting at Shirley's Sandwiches right now.
人民群众各种惊慌失措
Everyone freaking out.
新来的女人是恶魔
New lady is evil.
[表情]疯狂皱眉
Crazy frown.
我得走了
I should go.
阿布蒂  我想我很需要有人能帮忙
Abed, I could really use someone's help
摸清这儿的内情
in learning the ropes around here.
我会四处打探一下的
I'll ask around.
朋友  傻帽
Friends, dumb hats.
瞧瞧她那高人一等的口气
Totally talking down to you.
她讨厌你
She hates you.
杰拉德和我说的
I got it from Jared.
你们躲在这里做什么呢
What are you guys doing back here?
你们在演「大寒」里的情节吗
Are you the Big Chilling?
没错  只不过我们聚在一起抱怨的对象
Yeah, only there's not a hippie that died
不是什么死掉的嬉皮士
to make us come together and complain.
而是咱们的学校
It's our school.
弗兰已经接管校园了
Frankie's taking over the campus.
她取消了梯子课  禁用药物
She cancelled ladder's, she's banning substances,
她想要关闭雪瑞三明治
she wants to shut down Shirley's Sandwiches.
她还叫安妮贱人
She called Annie a bitch.
她暗示说我是个贱人
She implied I was a bitch.
她暗示说安妮是个傲慢自大
She implied Annie was a stuck up bitch
认为自己优秀到无人能比的婊子
who thinks she's better than everyone.
好吧  现在你是在...
Okay, now you're just...
她对我还挺友好的
She was nice to me.
其实我们相处得还算不错
In fact we kinda got along.
阿布蒂  你确定她不是在屈尊故作亲切吗
Abed, are you sure she wasn't actually being sweetly condescending?
不是  我已经学会分辨那个了
Yup, I learned to pick up on that one.
我要带头领导组建一个单独的秘密委员会
I make a movement that we form a separate, secret, committee.
我支持布雷塔的动议  但不赞同她领导
I second Britta's motion, not movement.
我赞成安妮对布雷塔的支「屎」
I third Annie's number two-ing of the movement Brita made.
恶心
Gross.
我们的任务就是保留真正的格林德尔
Our mission to preserve the real Greendale.
反对弗兰或喝酒
Oppose Frankie or drink.
哪个简单做哪个
Whatever's easiest.
你们确定她就是坏人了吗
Are you guys sure she's bad?
你们确定自己不是在重蹈我的覆辙
Are you sure you're not doing what I usually do,
对改变反应过度
overreacting to change?
这里没人会跟你一样  阿布蒂
Nobody's ever doing what you usually do Abed.
你是怪胎
You're nuts.
是褒义啦
In a good way.
我就是说说
I'm just saying.
把现实交给我们就好
Leave reality to us.
我们总是支持你的
We always support you.
别搞得那么狗血好吗
Don't make it more dramatic than it is.
这是我们对抗恶魔的血誓
It's a blood oath to defy evil.
你要么加入要么退出
You're either in or you're out.
我能不发血誓仍然和你们一起玩耍吗
Can I hang around if I don't do the oath.
老天  你是指我们只做朋友
Oh, Gee. You mean just be friends?
当然  没问题  阿布蒂
Sure. Great, Abed.
好的
Okay.
那我能吃点小脆饼干吗
Can I have some pretzels?
不行
No.
这是秘密委员会小脆饼干
Those are secret committee pretzels.
好吧
Okay.
刚刚只是个测试
Yes, that was a test.
你们真是一群糟糕的朋友
You guys are bad friends.
不要把这个当成烤焦的汉堡
Don't think of it as bad baking.
要把它想象成对于性别歧视的致命打击
Think of it as a crushing blow to a gender stereotype.
布雷塔  如果所有烤焦的三明治上面
Britta, it might help if every burnt sandwich
不带有自我意识的话估计会有所帮助
didn't come with a self-aware burnt sandwich bit.
你就是这样帮助提高销量的  创意点子
Is that how you're gonna help increase sales, creative notes?
酷耍广告牌的创意就是我想出来的
I had that sign spinner idea.
安妮  咱就是个学校食堂的小吃摊
We're a restaurant inside a cafeteria Annie,
我们的弱项显然不是交通问题
our weak point wasn't traffic.
弗洛  爱丽丝  喜剧「爱丽丝」中的角色
弗洛  爱丽丝  别掐架了
Flo, Alice stop fighting,
咱可输不起这地方
can't afford to lose this place.
如果我开始在男厕里开始喝酒
If I have to start drinking in the men's room,
特伦特·雷兹  摇滚乐队九寸钉的主唱
约翰尼·卡什  美国乡村音乐创作歌手
我脑中的音乐会从特伦特·雷兹原唱
the score in my head has to change from Trent Reznor
变成约翰尼·卡什的翻唱版了
to Johnny Cash doing Trent Reznor.
我是当酒保的  安妮
I'm a bartender Annie,
我还是了解一些人性化服务知识的
I know a little bit more about the human side of service.
我实在吃不下去
I can't eat this.
能把钱退给我吗
Can I have my money back?
你就是个人渣
You're human garbage.
你好  翁格先生
Hi, Mr. Winger.
昨天的讲座很棒
Nice lecture yesterday.
别拍我的马屁  混球
Don't patronize me dick.
也许看起来不是这样
It might not seem like this,
但你正在扼杀一个黑人经营的渺小生意
but you're killing small, black owned business.
如果能和翁格先生喝杯酒  我们就扯平了
I'll call it even for a drink with Mr. Winger.
-太荒唐了吧  -是吗
- That's absurd. - You will?
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
拿身份证来  敢去告密你就死定了
Let's see some ID. You snitch, you die.
早上好
Morning.
我想要先先等下其他人再开始了
Well I guess we'll wait for the others before we start.
-我不认为他们还会来  -什么
- I don't think they're coming. - What?
委员会昨晚开会表决了你是恶魔
The committee had a meeting last night and decided you are evil.
稍等  你们昨晚开会了
Ooh. Wait, you guys had a meeting last night?
所以我们已经不再是朋友了
So, we broke up as friends.
因为我并不认为你是恶魔
Because I don't think you're evil.
我想你让人害怕
I think you scare people,
是因为你生活在现实中而不是幻想
because you live in the real world instead of up your butt.
我真的很抱歉  阿布蒂
I'm sorry that happened, Abed.
就像我昨天在午餐时说过的
It's like I said yesterday at lunch.
戏剧和冲突总是简单和令人愉悦的
Drama and conflict are exciting and easy.
但想要做出不同就会很无聊
Making a difference can be pretty boring.
你们一起吃了午餐
You guys had lunch?
我想尝试着在那个世界里活下去
I'd like to try to live in that world.
我对这些戏剧什么的有点厌倦了
I'm a little tired from all the drama,
英雄啦  反派啦  怪兽啦
the heroes, the villains, monsters.
口袋妖怪啦
Pokemons.
而你能通过表象看到他们的本质
You're just a person that sees things the way they are.
地精啦  吓人吧
Leprechauns. Scary.
我不确定我能不能变成那样  但是
I don't know if I can be like that but
我同意不认为和它对着干是正确的
I don't think it makes sense to be against it.
你们听说过森林暗鬼吗
You guys ever hear of The Slender Man?
我想试着帮助你
I'd like to try to help you.
当然  如果可能的话  向你学习
And if possible, learn from you.
你们上Reddit论坛或4Chan吗
You guys on Reddit, 4Chan?
-那真是太好了  阿布蒂  -论坛超棒
- That would be great, Abed. - Cuz it's awesome.
如果大家都像你一样  那对所有人都好
I think we'd all benefit if we were more like you,
你觉得呢
so what do you say?
我们订个餐吧
Let's order some food.
让我们一起拯救格林德尔
Let's save Greendale.
让我们拯救格林德尔
玉米卷
Tacos!
我们还真是与众不同
We are something else.
阿布蒂
Abed.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
什么意思
What do you mean?
有人告诉我你在扫垃圾  摆正时钟
Someone told me you were sweeping, straightening clocks.
你为什么要清理掉那个标志
Why are you cleaning that sign?
我给了你一个清单
I gave you a list.
是啊  清单看起来都相似的
Yeah, the list felt pretty similar visually.
我想象不出来怎么剪辑
I can't picture a montage cutting from
从我确认黛安给我开发票
me verifying Diane's invoice to me
到我给她发确认邮件的蒙太奇
emailing confirmation to Diane.
好吧
Right.
蒙太奇是啥玩意儿  阿布蒂
But a montage is what, Abed?
是对现实致歉的电影
It's a movie apologizing for reality.
那我们在哪
And we are where?
-现实  -人们在现实做什么
- Reality. - And what do people do here?
给黛安发邮件吗
They email Diane?
黛安  确认下你收到了这些发票
阿布蒂  如果你今天再换衣服就给我走人
Abed, if you change your clothes one more time today, you're fired.
对不起
Sorry.
阿布蒂
Hey, Abed.
托德
Hey, Todd.
安妮和布雷塔在吗
Are Annie and Britta  around?
不在
No.
阿布蒂  或许你该点个特餐
Abed, maybe you should order the special.
我会点的
I'll have the special.
特餐放在后厨了
The specials are kept in the back.
你应该  你应该去后面看一眼
You should, you should go in the back.
警告
我想要那个特价菜
I'd like the special.
烟具  彩虹糖
Vaporizers, Skittles?
阿布蒂
Abed.
安妮
Hey, Annie.
这地方真有格调
This place is so conceptual.
同时也很实际
It's practical, too.
我们赚够了钱可以拯救雪瑞的店了
We made enough money to save Shirley's.
以一种讽刺的方式
And in an ironic way.
如果雪瑞看见了这个  她会气死的
Because if Shirley saw this, her soul would die.
阿布蒂  来看看这个
Hey, Abed, check this out.
布雷塔还是最烂的吗
Oh, Britta's still the worst?
是啊
Yeah.
酒吧越来越脏了
The bar gets dirty.
你得找个人去清理下  或许是下班之后
You're gonna need someone to clean it, probably after hours.
因为地板抛光机的噪音挺大的
And those floor polishers can get pretty loud.
我不喜欢让人听见这个噪音
I'd hate for someone to hear it.
你要敲诈我吗
You blackmailing me?
瞎说说而已
Just talking shop.
有什么骚乱  阿布蒂
What's the rumpus, Abed?
「黑帮龙虎斗」
Miller's Crossing.
这太棒了
This is really great.
你们这群家伙应该自豪点
You guys should be proud of yourselves.
我们想你了
We missed you.
喝杯酒吧
Have a drink.
穿套老式的夹克吧
Put on an old timey jacket.
好的  我不会再这么做了
That's okay, I don't really do this anymore.
好的  来
All right, come on.
我都说了  我不想这么干
I said I don't do this, see.
你个卑鄙小人
You dirty rat.
男的都是卑鄙小人
Guys are all dirty rats.
你的「碰跳教室」呢[70年代儿童节目]
What's your romper room?
好吧  就喝一杯
All right, maybe just one drink.
然后就剪成之后喝酒的蒙太奇
Then maybe cut to a montage of drinks.
咱以后一直还是朋友
Let's never stop being friends again ever.
干杯
Cheers!
我们不应该逼你在弗兰和我们之间抉择的
We shouldn't have made you choose between Frankie and us.
她对我们的生意有好处
Oh, she's good for business.
很抱歉逼你选择...
We're sorry that we made you choose between-
你就是把我说的重复了一遍
You're just repeating what I said.
不  是你重复了我说的
No, you're repeating what I said.
难道我会穿越吗
Oh, I'm a time traveler?
人生如戏啊
This is the show.
阿布蒂  我刚从黛安那得到消息
Abed, I just got word from Diane
你的某个邮件有点不靠谱
that one of your emails was a little shaky.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
好得很  昨天睡太晚
I'm good. Late night last night.
我去补充点蛋白质
Yeah, I could use a little protein.
我要早点去吃午餐
I'm gonna go get an early lunch.
你们几个知道什么是水熊虫吗
You guys know about tardigrades?
它们是一种像机器熊一样的微生物
They're these microscopic creatures that look like robot bears.
能在太空中生存
They can survive in space.
进入太空  你个小脏虫子
Get into space, you dirty tardigrades, see?
它们无处不在
And they're everywhere.
现实生活中有很多虚拟生物一样酷的小生命
There's a lot of little things in real life
that are just as cool as fake stuff.
我为弗兰工作的时候学到了这个
I learned that working for Frankie.
你们会喜欢她的
You guys would like her, you know.
突袭检查
Raid!
这就是你们想要的吗
Is this what you guys want?
你们想穿上戏服  玩警察抓小偷是吗
You wanna play cops and robbers with costumes?
为什么那个人扮成胡萝卜
Why is that guy a carrot?
因为警服都穿完了
Because they ran out.
谁泄露了机密
Who tattled?
布雷塔  在你认为这点儿小秘密
In what world, Brita, do you see this as covert
犯得上泄露吗
enough to require tattling?
你在学校里开了个酒吧
You built a bar in a school.
职责所在啊
There was lumber involved.
我让你们能躲到这
I have been letting you hole up down here,
因为这样让你们感到从容舒适
because it kept you contained and satisfied,
因为你们总是挑衅  这还不够
because you are all compulsively defiant, but it wasn't enough.
你们又把阿布蒂拉进来  阿布蒂理应更好
You had to drag Abed back in, and Abed deserves better.
看啊  终于露出尾巴了
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, it finally comes out.
阿布蒂理应更好
Abed deserves better.
这事早就公开了
That's been out.
闭嘴  伦纳德
Shut up, Leonard.
有回在药店  一连六个老头我都错认成了你
I once mistook six people for you at a pharmacy.
弗兰  这不是他们的错
It's not their fault, Frankie.
我选择这样
I chose this.
他们是我的朋友
These are my friends.
我讨厌给黛安写邮件
I hate emailing Diane.
她不能老是改字体
She can't commit to a font.
真是有病  我也是
It's pathological, and so am I.
这才是我的归属
This is where I belong.
我知道你是这么想的  阿布蒂
I know you think that, Abed,
但你什么都不知道
but you don't know any better.
闭嘴  伦纳德
But shut up, Leonard.
你也是
You are.
你个老头子
You are old.
因为你老  所以你不配
And you deserve less, because of your age.
我不是这么想的
I don't, I don't actually believe that.
我只是在...只是在  这里的人
I'm just trying to, I'm trying to, and everybody here is a,
都是屁
is a fart,
都是次等神屁眼里放出的大臭屁
a livid fart from the butt of a lesser God.
我本该用点更好的比喻
I'm, I'm better than this.
切到校园里人人豪饮的蒙太奇场景
Cut to everyone on campus getting as drunk as they want montage.
弗兰今天没来上班
Frankie hasn't come back to work today.
真是太糟了
That's terrible.
保险公司不要我们了
The insurance company dropped us.
我们学校现在连保险都没了
The school has no insurance.
弗兰的薪水怎么样
What was Frankie's salary?
很多
A lot.
那保险费呢
What were the insurance premiums?
也很多
A lot.
那两个加一起就是新的舞会预算
Add those two numbers together, that's your new school dance budget.
真棒
Oh, nice.
欢迎来到梯子课
Welcome to ladder!
棒哦
Yeah!
梯子
Ladder!
要不要看看梯子老师爬得更高
Who wants to see the ladders professor go higher?
梯子
Ladder!
你成功了  杰夫·翁格
You did it, Jeff Winger!
这是你的学校了
This is your school now.
安妮
Annie.
值了
It was worth it.
好  教授的治疗费用应该就这么多了
All right, that should be the extent of the professor's medical bills.
那学生的诉讼呢
What, what about that lawsuits from the students?
这官司得打
I think we should fight those.
我觉得庭外和解比较好
Actually, I suggest you settle out of court.
都是我的错
This is my fault.
当然不是
Obviously not.
-是我的错  -是我的错
- It's my fault. - It's my fault.
伙计们  是我的错
Guys, it's my fault.
是我的错
It's my fault.
好了  好了  好了
All right, all right, all right.
这事儿谁没错呢
So, whose fault wasn't it?
有谁知道怎么处理这堆麻烦吗
And who knows anything about handling anything like this?
至于等级制度  我是十分推崇的
In terms of hierarchy, I'm a big believer in it.
如果要有人领头  那个人必须是我
Someone needs to say, I'm in charge, and that person is me.
得由我说了算
That's my decision.
什么玩意儿
Wait, what?
-怎么了  -谁会这么说话啊
- I'm sorry? - Who talks like that?
天下怎么会有如此浮夸的女子
Why would anyone hire someone so pompous?
达特女士  听我一句劝
Miss Dart, word of advice,
你最好改改你的脾气  不然就去
change your personality, or start looking for
找一家疯子公司吧
companies run by insane people.
别雇这个女人
Don't hire this woman.
事不过五
Fifth time's the charm.
他之前已经闯入四间办公室  大吼大叫
He's barged the four offices screaming,
别雇这个女人
don't hire this woman.
搞什么鬼
What the hell is going on?
你们怎么来了
What are you doing here?
又是怎么找到我的
How did you even find me?
我给黛安写了邮件
I emailed Diane.
她真是太了解你的日程了
She knows way too much about your schedule, by the way.
不管他给你开了什么条件  格林德尔
Whatever he's offering you, Greendale, well,
给不了你双倍
we can't double it.
甚至给不了相同的薪水
We probably can't even match it.
但不管他给你开了什么条件
Whatever he's offering you,
格林德尔只能给你更少  外加一个道歉
Greendale will give you less, and an apology.
你们知不知道
Do you know...
这不够  不过...
It's not enough, but
你们如果能给我多一点道歉
maybe if you added more apologies.
蒙太奇叠加式的道歉吗
Like a montage of them?
对不起
We're sorry.
我说了  今晚我不用晚餐
I told you I wouldn't be needing dinner tonight.
我猜你也不会
I'm guessing you wouldn't.
因为你在找这个
Not if you're looking for this.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
面包屑之于厨师
Nobody makes more crumbs than a cook.
正如线索之于侦探
Well, the same goes for clues and detectives.
你这么执迷于破案  自己想了断却不上心
You're too busy solving murders to get away with your own.
那我妻子的案子呢  还有我的腿呢  雪瑞
Well, then, what about the case of my wife and my legs, Shirley?
你也能破了吗
Can you solve that one, huh?
你能吗
Can you?
如果你破不了  那我也生无可恋了
Cuz if you can't, then I ain't got nothing to live for.
对不起  布彻先生
Begging your pardon, Mr. Butcher.
你这么说  整个海湾的人都不会信
I think the people on this bayou would disagree.
你今天救了一位出走的姑娘
You rescued a runaway girl today.
救什么救啊
Rescued, balls.
现在就是换个灯泡我都无能为力
I couldn't even rescue a, a bulb from a socket.
今天的活儿难道不都是你干的吗
And you did all the work today, didn't you?
我只是亚特兰大这鬼地方里的
I'm just a detective from the swamps of Atlanta,
一个走不了路的侦探
can't even walk.
那就让我当你的腿吧
Then let me be your legs.
以后我都会像今天一样
Let me do for you what
直到你找到妻子
I did today every week until you find your wife.
重新站起来
Or your legs.
你真是倔得跟头牛似的  雪瑞·伯纳德
You are a stubborn son of a bitch, Shirley Bennett.
快起来吧  我还要做晚餐呢
Now come on. I have dinner to make.
而你  还有案子要破
You got cases to solve.
今晚那些马铃薯要性命不保了
Feeling someone's gonna murder some tater tots tonight.
这点毫无疑问了
That's no mystery at all.
下周 「布彻与大厨」
Next week, on The Butcher and the Baker,
亚特兰大新来的侦探失踪
when a new detective on the Bayou disappears,
布彻成了首要嫌疑人
and Butcher is the prime suspect,
雪瑞大厨又要寻找真相了
it's up to Shirley to cook up some answers.
■
最新美剧下载请登录字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
扫描左边二维码关注我们的微信号
或搜索微信号: ustvboom
非常欢迎爱好者加入字幕组一起翻译海外影视剧
■
你看懂了吗
Did you get any of that?